A Guide to the General Thomas L. Rosser And Rosser Family Papers, 1774-1983
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Series V: Bound Volumes
  - Vol. 33: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1905 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 34: Diary, w/accounts, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1906 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 35: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1907 (Box Box 19)
  - Loose items from Volume 35 1906-1907 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 36: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1908 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 37: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1909 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 38: Memoranda book, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1910 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 39: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1911 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 40: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1912 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 41: Memoranda Book 1912 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 42: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1913 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 43: Diary of [Elizabeth W. Rosser] 1913-1914 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 44: Diary, Barbara Rosser 1913-1915 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 45: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1914 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 46: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1915 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 47: Diary [Barbara Rosser?]--loose pages 1916 Mar 20-Apr 31 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 48: Diary of [Thomas L. Rosser, Jr.] 1916 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 49: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1917 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 50: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1918 (Box Box 19)
  - Vol. 51: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1919 (Box Box 20)
  - Vol. 52: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1919 (Box Box 20)
  - Vol. 53: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1920-1921 Jan 28 (Box Box 20)
  - Vol. 54: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1921 (Box Box 20)
  - Vol. 55: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1922-1923 Jan 3 (Box Box 20)
  - Vol. 56: Memoranda Book, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1922-1927 (Box Box 20)
  - Vol. 57: Diary, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1924 (Box Box 20)
  - Vol. 58: Memoranda Book, T. L. Rosser, Jr. 1924 (Box Box 20)
  - Vol. 59: Letter Book, Barbara W. Rosser ("The Branch, University, Va.") Peoples National Bank, University 1965 (Box Box 20)
  - Vol. 60: Memoranda Book, Gen. Thomas L. Rosser, Jr.(?) n.d. (Box Box 20)
- Series VI: Oversize
  - Lithograph of a Jefferson Davis letter, November 21, 1889, re an invitation for him to attend centennial observances of North Carolina's ratification of the Constitution 1896
  - Blueprint map showing Mercedita, Corojab, Bahia Honda, etc. ca. 1899
  - "Plano De La Habana" (Cuba) ca. 1899
  - Appointment certificate of Thomas L. Rosser as postmaster of Charlottesville in Albemarle County, signed, President Theodore Roosevelt 1905 Feb 25
  - Commission, Thomas S. Rosser [Thomas L. Rosser, Jr.?], as "a delegate to represent the State of Virginia at the World's Diary Congress," signed, Governor E. Lee Trinkle 1923 Aug 2
  - Broadside, "High-Class Residential Sites A Part of Rugby Just Off Rugby Road, Charlottesville, Va." n.d.
  - Broadside, "25 Beautiful Homesties On and New Rugby Road Close to the University To Be Sold At Auction" n.d.
  - Map, "Puerto de Bahia Honda" (Cuba) n.d.
  - Oversize Photographs
  - The Chi Phi's [University of Virginia, Old Cabell Hall] 1886-1887
  - Fraternity group of ten men and a dog in front of the University of Virginia Chapel ca. 1890s
  - Fraternity group of nineteen men in front of a University of Virginia pavilion ca. 1890s
  - Fraternity group of sixteen men on the Lawn at the University of Virginia ca. 1890s
  - General Thomas L. Rosser (center) with a group of ten other men ca. 1900
  - Photograph of participants at the reunion and dinner of the "Northern Pacific Pioneers Rosser, Jr. of 1873 and Earlier"--includes T. L. 1906 Jan 6
  - "Brito To Greytown 173.57 miles" 1882, (horizontal view, 16 1/2 feet long)
  - Blueprint map, "Charlottesville Water Works Moorman's River Extension" 1923 Dec
  - A German map of middle Europe n.d.
  - Incomplete map, "Township No 121 N[orth] Range N[orth] 23 West, 5th Mer[idian] and Township No 120 N[orth] Range N[orth] 23 West, 5th Mer[idian]" n.d.
  - "Map of Water-View, Gloucester Co. Va." n.d.
  - Members of the Virginia Club; includes T. L. Rosser, Jr. (seventh from right)--photograph by R. W. Holsinger ca. 1920s